Guide to the Chancellor of the University of Pittsburgh, J. Dennis O'Connor, Administrative Files, 1991-1995 UA.2.10.1991-1995
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Mail Log Files, 1991-1995; I.
  - Senior Vice Chancellor for Business & Finance and Treasurer, 11.
    - University Planning and Budgeting Committee, 11.3.5.
      - 11.3.5. University Planning and Budgeting Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - 11.3.5. University Planning and Budgeting Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 18-22)
      - 11.3.5. University Planning and Budgeting Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
      - 11.3.5. University Planning and Budgeting Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - 11.3.5. University Planning and Budgeting Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Budgets, 11.3.6.
      - 11.3.6. FY95 Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - 11.3.6. FY96 Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Office of Institutional Research, 11.3.7.
      - 11.3.7. Office of Institutional Research, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - 11.3.7. Office of Institutional Research, 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 8-9)
    - Central Business Support Services, 11.4.
      - 11.4. Central Business Support Services, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - 11.4. Central Business Support Services, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Child Development Center, 11.5.
      - 800.20. Child Development Center, 1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - 11.5. Child Development Center, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - 11.5. Child Development Center, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - 11.5. Child Development Center, 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Comptroller, 11.6.
      - 702.02. Comptroller, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 16-17)
      - 11.6. Comptroller, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 18-19)
      - 11.6. Comptroller, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 20-21)
      - 11.6. Comptroller, 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - 11.6. Comptroller, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
    - Computing and Information Systems, 11.7.
      - 11.7. Computing and Information Systems, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - 11.7. Computing and Information Systems, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - 11.7. Computing and Information Systems, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Telecommunications, 11.7.1.
      - 11.7.1. Telecommunications, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - 11.7.1. Telecommunications, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - EDUCOM, 11.7.2.
      - 11.7.2. EDUCOM, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Supercomputing Center, 11.7.3.
      - 800.11. Pittsburgh Supercomputing Center, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - 11.7.3. Pittsburgh Supercomputing Center, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - 11.7.3. Pittsburgh Supercomputing Center, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 11-12)
      - 11.7.3. Pittsburgh Supercomputing Center, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 13-14)
    - Facilities Management, 11.8.
      - 703.00. Associate Vice President of Facilities Management, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 15-18)
      - 11.8. Facilities Management, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 19-20)
      - 11.8. Facilities Management, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
      - 11.8. Facilities Management, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 3-9)
      - 11.8. Facilities Management, 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 10-13)
    - Environmental Health and Safety, 11.8.1.
      - 11.8.1. Environmental Health and Safety, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - 11.8.1. Environmental Health and Safety, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - 11.8.1. Environmental Health and Safety, 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Property Management, 11.8.2.
      - 703.01. Property Management, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - 11.8.2. Property Management, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - 11.8.2. Property Management, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - 11.8.2. Property Management, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - 11.8.2. Property Management, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Office of Technology Transfer and Intellectual Property, 11.8.3.
      - 11.8.3. Office of Technology Transfer and Intellectual Property, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - 11.8.3. Office of Technology Transfer and Intellectual Property, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - 11.8.3. Office of Technology Transfer and Intellectual Property, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - 11.8.3. Office of Technology Transfer and Intellectual Property, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Operation Jump Start, 11.8.4.
      - 11.8.4. Operation Jump Start, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - 11.8.4. Operation Jump Start, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - 11.8.4. Operation Jump Start, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Parking and Transportation, 11.8.5.
      - 11.8.5. Parking and Transportation, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - 11.8.5. Parking and Transportation, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Human Resources, 11.9.
      - 701.06. Human Resources, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - 11.9. Human Resources, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - 11.9. Human Resources, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - 11.9. Human Resources, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - 11.9. Human Resources, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Benefits, 11.9.1.
      - 11.9.1. Benefits, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - 11.9.1. Benefits, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 21-22)
      - 11.9.1. Benefits, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 23-24)
      - 11.9.1. Benefits, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Staff Association Council (SAC), 11.9.3.
      - 701.06B. Staff Association Council, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 26)
      - 11.9.2. Staff Association Council, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 27)
      - 11.9.2. Staff Association Council, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - 11.9.2. Staff Association Council, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Domestic Partnerships, 11.9.4.
      - 11.9.4. Domestic Partnerships, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 30-31)
      - 11.9.4. Domestic Partnerships, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Management Information Policy Analysis (MIPA), 11.10.
      - 701.08. Management Information Policy Analysis (MIPA), 1991-1992 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
      - 11.10. Management Information Policy Analysis (MIPA), 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - 11.10. Management Information Policy Analysis (MIPA), 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 4-5)
      - 11.10. Management Information Policy Analysis (MIPA), 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Organization Charts, 11.10.1.
      - 701.08. Organization Charts, 1991-1992 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - 11.10.1. Organization Charts, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - 11.10.1. Organization Charts, 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - 11.10.1. Organization Charts, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Public Safety, 11.11.
      - 701.02. Public Safety, 1991-1992 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - 11.11. Public Safety, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - 11.11. Public Safety, 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - 11.11. Public Safety, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - 11.11. Public Safety, 1995-1996 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Student Registration and Financial Services, 11.12.
      - 11.12. Student Registration and Financial Services, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - 11.12. Student Registration and Financial Services, 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Registrar, 11.12.1.
      - 11.12.1. Registrar, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Internal Audit, 11.13.
      - 11.13. Internal Audit, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 19-21)
      - 11.13. Internal Audit, 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 22-23)
      - 11.13. Internal Audit, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 24-25)
      - 11.13. Internal Audit, 1995-1996 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - University Counsel, 11.14.
      - 707.00. University Counsel, 1991-1992 (Box 51, Folder 27)
      - 11.14. University Counsel, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - 11.14. University Counsel, 1993-1994 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - 11.14. University Counsel, 1994-1995 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - 11.14. University Counsel, 1995-1996 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Commonwealth Relations, 11.15.
      - 203.00. Commonwealth Relations, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 5-7)
      - 203.00. Legislative Hearing Briefing Book, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - 203.00. FY93 Planning and Budgeting Documents - President/Administration, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - 203.00. FY93 Planning and Budgeting Documents - Provost, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 10-12)
      - 203.00. FY93 Planning and Budgeting Documents - Health Sciences, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - 203.00. FY93 Planning and Budgeting Documents - Total University and Responsibility Center Profiles, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - 11.15. Commonwealth Relations, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 15-16)
      - 11.15. Commonwealth Relations, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 1-5)
      - 11.15. Commonwealth Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 53, Folder 6-13)
      - 11.15. Commonwealth Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 54, Folder 1-3)
      - 11.15. Commonwealth Relations, 1994-1995 (Box 54, Folder 4-13)
      - 11.15. Commonwealth Relations, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
      - 11.15. Task Force on Higher Education Funding, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 3-4)
      - Task Force on Higher Education Funding recording, November 29, 1994 (Audio-cabinet 2-7, Cassette 1)
      - 11.15. Commonwealth Relations, 1995-1996 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Office of the Governor, 11.15.1.
      - 11.15.1. Office of the Governor, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - 11.15.1. Office of the Governor, 1993-1994 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - 11.15.1. Office of the Governor, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Education, 11.15.2.
      - 203.02. Pennsylvania Department of Education, 1991-1992 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - 11.15.2. Pennsylvania Department of Education, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
      - 11.15.2. Pennsylvania Department of Education, 1993-1994 (Box 55, Folder 12-14)
      - 11.15.2. Pennsylvania Department of Education, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 15-18)
    - Pennsylvania Economic Development Partnership, 11.15.3.
      - 203.01A. Pennsylvania Economic Development Partnership, 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - 11.15.3. Pennsylvania Economic Development Partnership, 1992-1993 (Box 56, Folder 2-3)
      - 11.15.3. Pennsylvania Economic Development Partnership, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 4-5)
      - 11.15.3. Pennsylvania Economic Development Partnership, 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Associations and Organizations, 12.
    The material in the 12.0 Mail Log files relates to the various associations and organizations to which the University of Pittsburgh and Chancellor O'Connor belonged or with whom they interacted. They include meeting minutes, publications, and correspondence of organizations, as well as event information in some cases. Of particular interest here are the files concerning the Allegheny Conference on Community Development (12.01), which provides a look into the university's expanding role in the region.
    - Associations and Organizations, 12.0.
      - 1000.00. Associations and Organizations, 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - 12.0. Associations and Organizations, 1992-1993 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - 12.0. Associations and Organizations, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 9-10)
      - 12.0. Associations and Organizations, 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 11-13)
    - Allegheny Conference on Community Development (ACCD), 12.1.
      - 1001.00. Allegheny Conference on Community Development (ACCD), 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - 12.1. Allegheny Conference on Community Development (ACCD), 1992-1993 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - 12.1. Allegheny Conference on Community Development (ACCD), 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - 12.1. Allegheny Conference on Community Development (ACCD), 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - 12.1. Allegheny Conference on Community Development (ACCD), 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 2-3)
      - 12.1. Allegheny Conference on Community Development (ACCD), 1995-1996 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - American Assembly, 12.2.
      - 12.2. American Assembly, 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), 12.3.
      - 12.3. American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 12.4.
      - 12.4. American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - 12.4. American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - 12.4. American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), 12.5.
      - 1034.00. American Council of Learned Societies, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - 12.5. American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - 12.5. American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - American Council on Education (ACE), 12.6.
      - 1005.00. American Council on Education (ACE), 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - 12.6. American Council on Education (ACE), 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - 12.6. American Council on Education (ACE), 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 15-16)
      - 12.6. American Council on Education (ACE), 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 17-18)
    - Association of American Colleges (AAC), 12.7.
      - 12.7. Association of American Colleges (AAC), 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - 12.7. Association of American Colleges (AAC), 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU), 12.8.
      - 1008.00. Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 57, Folder 21)
      - 12.8. Association of American Universities (AAU), 1992-1993 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
      - 12.8. Association of American Universities (AAU), 1993-1994 (Box 58, Folder 4-12)
      - 12.8. Association of American Universities (AAU), 1993-1994 (Box 59, Folder 1-5)
      - 12.8. Association of American Universities (AAU), 1994-1995 (Box 59, Folder 6-12)
      - 12.8. Association of American Universities (AAU), 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 1-8)
      - 12.8. Association of American Universities (AAU), 1995-1996 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - AAU Committee on Technology Transfer and Intellectual Property, 12.8.1.
      - 12.8.1. AAU Committee on Technology Transfer and Intellectual Property, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - 12.8.1. AAU Committee on Technology Transfer and Intellectual Property, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - AAU Committee on Post-Doctoral Education, 12.8.2.
      - 12.8.2. AAU Committee on Post-Doctoral Education, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - 12.8.2. AAU Committee on Post-Doctoral Education, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 13-14)
    - Association of Governing Boards, 12.9.
      - 1009.00. Association of Governing Boards, 1991-1992 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - 12.9. Association of Governing Boards, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - 12.9. Association of Governing Boards, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - 12.9. Association of Governing Boards, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - 12.9. Association of Governing Boards, 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 2-4)
      - 12.9. Association of Governing Boards, 1995-1996 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Business Higher Education Forum (BHEF), 12.10.
      - 1005.01. Business Higher Education Forum (BHEF), 1991-1992 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - 12.10. Business Higher Education Forum (BHEF), 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - 12.10. Business Higher Education Forum (BHEF), 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 8-10)
      - 12.10. Business Higher Education Forum (BHEF), 1995-1996 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency, 12.12.
      - 12.12. Center for the Study of the Presidency, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - 12.12. Center for the Study of the Presidency, 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - College and University Personnel Association (CUPA), 12.13.
      - 12.13. College and University Personnel Association (CUPA), 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Consortium of Social Science Association (COSSA), 12.14.
      - 12.14. Consortium of Social Science Association (COSSA), 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - 12.14. Consortium of Social Science Association (COSSA), 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Council for Advancement and Support of Education (CASE), 12.15.
      - 12.15. Council for Advancement and Support of Education (CASE), 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - 12.15. Council for Advancement and Support of Education (CASE), 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Council on Competitiveness, 12.16.
      - 12.16. Council on Competitiveness, 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Council on Research and Technology (CORETECH), 12.18.
      - 12.18. Council on Research and Technology (CORETECH), 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - International Association of Universities (IAU), 12.19.
      - 12.19. International Association of Universities (IAU), 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - 12.19. International Association of Universities (IAU), 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - 12.19. International Association of Universities (IAU), 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools (MSA), 12.23.
      - 1035.00. Middles States Association of Colleges and Schools (MSA), 1991-1992 (Box 61, Folder 24-25)
      - 12.23. Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools (MSA), 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 26)
      - 12.23. Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools (MSA), 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 27-28)
      - 12.23. Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools (MSA), 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 12.24.
      - 12.24. National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 30)
      - 12.24. National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 1-4)
      - 12.24. National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 12.26.
      - 12.26. National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - 12.26. National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews (NCCJ), 12.27.
      - 12.27. National Conference of Christians and Jews (NCCJ), 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Ohio River Basin Consortium for Research and Education, 12.29.
      - 12.29. Ohio River Basin Consortium for Research and Education, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Penn's Southwest Association, 12.30.
      - 12.30. Penn's Southwest Association, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - 12.30. Penn's Southwest Association, 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - 12.30. Penn's Southwest Association, 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 13-15)
    - Pennsylvania Association of Colleges and Universities (PACU), 12.31.
      - 1022.00. Pennsylvania Association of Colleges and Universities (PACU), 1991-1992 (Box 62, Folder 16)
      - 12.31. Pennsylvania Association of Colleges and Universities (PACU), 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 17-19)
      - 12.31. Pennsylvania Association of Colleges and Universities (PACU), 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - 12.31. Pennsylvania Association of Colleges and Universities (PACU), 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 2-6)
      - 12.31. Pennsylvania Association of Colleges and Universities (PACU), 1994-1995 (Box 63, Folder 7-12)
      - 12.31. Pennsylvania Association of Colleges and Universities (PACU), 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh Convention and Visitors Bureau, 12.32.
      - 12.32. Pittsburgh Convention and Visitors Bureau, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - 12.32. Pittsburgh Convention and Visitors Bureau, 1994-1995 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh Council on Higher Education (PCHE), 12.33.
      - 1025.00. Pittsburgh Council on Higher Education (PCHE), 1991-1992 (Box 63, Folder 16)
      - 12.33. Pittsburgh Council on Higher Education (PCHE), 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 17)
      - 12.33. Pittsburgh Council on Higher Education (PCHE), 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - 12.33. Pittsburgh Council on Higher Education (PCHE), 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 2-3)
    - Regional Industrial Development Corporation (RIDC), 12.34.
      - 12.34. Regional Industrial Development Corporation (RIDC), 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - 12.34. Regional Industrial Development Corporation (RIDC), 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - 12.34. Regional Industrial Development Corporation (RIDC), 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - The College Board, 12.35.
      - 12.35. The College Board, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - 12.35. The College Board, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - 12.35. The College Board, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - 12.35. The College Board, 1995-1996 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Universities Research Association (URA), 12.36.
      - 12.36. Universities Research Association, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - 12.36. Universities Research Association, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - 12.36. Universities Research Association, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh, 12.38.
      - 1033.00. World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - 12.38. World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - 12.38. World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 16-17)
      - 12.38. World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 18-19)
      - 12.38. World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh, 1995-1996 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 12.39.
      - 12.39. Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - 12.39. Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Pittsburgh High Technology Council, 12.40.
      - 12.40. Pittsburgh High Technology Council, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Jewish National Fund Tree of Life Dinner, 12.41.
      - 12.41. Jewish National Fund Tree of Life Dinner, 1995-1996 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Colleges and Universities, 13.
    The material in the 13.0 Mail Log primarily concerns other universities, such as Carnegie Mellon University, Penn State University, and Duquesne University. The materials here include correspondence between Chancellor O'Connor and his counterparts at the other institutions, as well as information on activities and job openings from the other schools.
    - Colleges and Universities, 13.0.
      - 1100.00. Colleges and Universities, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 25)
      - 13.0. Colleges and Universities, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 26)
      - 13.0. Colleges and Universities, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 27)
      - 13.0. Colleges and Universities, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 28)
      - 13.0. Colleges and Universities, 1995-1996 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Carnegie Mellon University (CMU), 13.1.
      - 1104.00. Carnegie Mellon University (CMU), 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 30)
      - 13.1. Carnegie Mellon University (CMU), 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 31)
      - 13.1. Carnegie Mellon University (CMU), 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 32)
      - 13.1. Carnegie Mellon University (CMU), 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Community College of Allegheny County, Chatham College, Point Park College, 13.2.
      - 1107.00. Community College of Allegheny County, Chatham College, Point Park College, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 34)
      - 13.2. Community College of Allegheny County, Chatham College, Point Park College, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 35)
      - 13.2. Community College of Allegheny County, Chatham College, Point Park College, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Duquesne University, 13.3.
      - 13.3. Duquesne University, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - Penn State University, 13.4.